hey they say huh Saturday afternoon the
gang has decided to go on a picnic
man Sonia I sure can't wait for Knuckles
a mini to arrive so we can go on the
picnic it'll be so fun
I know huh
he's selling your look wha over there
Knuckles is coming right now
sup guys sup NOx is Mindy with you no
she said she'll be here in a minute
let's just leave without we can't do
that see my best friend TK hey will you
guys really going to leave without me oh
of course not sugar tits
oh man you sure know how to flatter me
I'm not being in the ass - come on Gus
let's go to the picnic okay let's go
away first we need you think of what
we're gonna eat damn you rob
you're right sugar tits okay guys what
are we bringing to the picnic I think we
should take bologna sandwiches
Wow Sonia that's a good idea God God
look over there
what the you gotta do some brown
coat the picnic down for Nick what are
you doing oh how about Vic mm I was just
talking to my gunky bro
well hurry up and then over so I can
bang your ass yes Bobby oh you get a row
hey Bobby what are you doing with that
with that sausage I think you and I both
know what I'm going to do with the
sausage my cute little Oh